University Photography Photograph Collection UA206
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 2005 -- 2006; UA206.001; 3347 Digital Object(s)
  - Job 050520 MKO Packard, 2005; UA206.001.044; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 020, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00026; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 008, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00027; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 155, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00028; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 120, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00029; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 088, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00030; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 083, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00031; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 010, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00032; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 178, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00033; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 144, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00034; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 134, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00035; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 124, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00036; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 123, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00037; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 111, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00038; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 080, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00039; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 057, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00040; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 046, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00041; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 032, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00042; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 031, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00043; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 027, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00044; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 023, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00045; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 022, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00046; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 021, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00047; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 007, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00048; Ko, Melody
    - Packard Society Reception at Gifford House. Photo 001, 2005-05-20; UA206.001.044.00049; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050521 ACS Alumni Parade, 2005; UA206.001.045; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 025, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00001; Schutzengel, Aaron
      Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement.
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 007, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00002; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 014, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00003; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 002, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00004; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 017, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00005; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 006, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00006; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 042, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00007; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 027, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00008; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 048, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00009; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 040, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00010; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 021, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00011; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 054, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00012; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 034, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00013; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 046, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00014; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 033, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00015; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 030, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00016; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 028, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00017; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 022, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00018; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 020, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00019; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 018, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00020; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 013, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00021; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 012, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00022; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 008, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00023; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 005, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00024; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 004, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00025; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Alumni Parade during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 045, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.045.00026; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050521 ACS ROTC, 2005; UA206.001.046; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - ROTC Commissioning Ceremony in Goddard Chapel during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 038, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.046.00001; Schutzengel, Aaron
      ROTC Commissioning Ceremony in Goddard Chapel during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement.
    - ROTC Commissioning Ceremony in Goddard Chapel during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 044, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.046.00002; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - ROTC Commissioning Ceremony in Goddard Chapel during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 003, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.046.00003; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - ROTC Commissioning Ceremony in Goddard Chapel during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 033, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.046.00004; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - ROTC Commissioning Ceremony in Goddard Chapel during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 030, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.046.00005; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - ROTC Commissioning Ceremony in Goddard Chapel during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 010, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.046.00006; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - ROTC Commissioning Ceremony in Goddard Chapel during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 041, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.046.00007; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050521 MKO Baccalaureate, 2005; UA206.001.047; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050521 MKO Honorary Degree, 2005; UA206.001.048; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050521 NSO ROTC, 2005; UA206.001.049; Sobecki, Nicki
  - Job 050521 MKO Parents Reception, 2005; UA206.001.050; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 004, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00001; Ko, Melody
      Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement.
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 007, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00002; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 012, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00003; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 016, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00004; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 021, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00005; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 030, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00006; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 032, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00007; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 034, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00008; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 038, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00009; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 042, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00010; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 044, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00011; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 046, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00012; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 048, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00013; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 049, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00014; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 051, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00015; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 053, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00016; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 056, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00017; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 070, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00018; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 090, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00019; Ko, Melody
    - Reception for parents in the Coolidge Room during the weekend of the 2005 Commencement. Photo 093, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.050.00020; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050522 ASC Commencement, 2005; UA206.001.051; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 056, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00001; Schutzengel, Aaron
      Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony.
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 074, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00002; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 068, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00003; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 044, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00004; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 085, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00005; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 036, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00006; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 022, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00007; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 030, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00008; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 112, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00009; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 098, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00010; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 095, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00011; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 062, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00012; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 059, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00013; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 038, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00014; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 037, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00015; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 034, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00016; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 031, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00017; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 029, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00018; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 019, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00019; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 092, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.051.00020; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050522 JTO Commencement, 2005; UA206.001.052; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 216, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00001; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 196, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00002; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 050, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00003; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 019, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00004; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 010, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00005; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 203, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00006; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 048, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00007; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 123, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00008; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 037, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00009; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 147, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00010; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 021, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00011; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 210, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00012; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 207, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00013; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 186, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00014; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 175, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00015; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 159, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00016; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 157, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00017; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 046, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00018; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony. Photo 004, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.052.00019; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 050522 JTO Medical, 2005; UA206.001.053; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 2 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony for the School of Medicine in the Gantcher Center. Photo 017, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.053.00001; Tobin, Joanie
      Phase 2 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony for the School of Medicine in the Gantcher Center.
    - Phase 2 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony for the School of Medicine in the Gantcher Center. Photo 072, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.053.00002; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 2 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony for the School of Medicine in the Gantcher Center. Photo 026, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.053.00003; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 2 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony for the School of Medicine in the Gantcher Center. Photo 006, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.053.00004; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 2 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony for the School of Medicine in the Gantcher Center. Photo 025, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.053.00005; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 2 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony for the School of Medicine in the Gantcher Center. Photo 059, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.053.00006; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 2 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony for the School of Medicine in the Gantcher Center. Photo 005, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.053.00007; Tobin, Joanie
    - Phase 2 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony for the School of Medicine in the Gantcher Center. Photo 030, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.053.00008; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 050522 MKO Commencement, 2005; UA206.001.054; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 414, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00001; Ko, Melody
      Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel.
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 379, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00002; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 311, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00003; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 232, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00004; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 125, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00005; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 091, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00006; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 040, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00007; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 026, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00008; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 2031, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00009; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 2005, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00010; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1934, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00011; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1829, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00012; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1714, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00013; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1704, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00014; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1629, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00015; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1616, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00016; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1547, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00017; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1491, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00018; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1436, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00019; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1187, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00020; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1087, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00021; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 889, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00022; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 594, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00023; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 445, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00024; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 540, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00025; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 516, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00026; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 2016, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00027; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1995, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00028; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1936, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00029; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1879, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00030; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1868, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00031; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1791, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00032; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1731, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00033; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1729, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00034; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1728, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00035; Ko, Melody
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony, robing in the Coolidge Room and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 1720, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.054.00036; Ko, Melody